Guide to the Greenwall Foundation Archive 1976-2011 (bulk 1991-2010) MSS 336
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Subject Files
  - Ridge Theatre, 1994-2003 (Box 28, Folder 1-5)
  - Ripe Time, 2006-2010 (Box 28, Folder 6-8)
  - River Arts Repertory Company, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Riverside Shakespeare Company, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Riverside Symphony, 1990-1994 (Box 28, Folder 11-12)
  - Rotunda Gallery, The, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 13-14)
  - Roulette Intermedium, Inc, 1992-2010 (Box 28, Folder 15-25)
  - Ruby Shang and Company, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Rude Mechanicals Theater Company, 2004 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Saint Luke's Chamber Ensemble, 1989-1997 (Box 28, Folder 28-34)
  - Salt Theater, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Sarah Scaggs Dance Company, 1996-2001 (Box 28, Folder 36-39)
  - Saratoga International Theatre Institute, 1995-2001 (Box 28, Folder 40-41)
  - School of American Ballet, 1988-1992 (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Sculpture Center, 2003-2009 (Box 28, Folder 43-44)
  - Sculpture Center, 1992-2002 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
  - Sean Curran Company, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 7-9)
  - Second Stage Theatre, 1988-2002 (Box 29, Folder 10-15)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, 1991-1999 (Box 29, Folder 16-19)
  - Sens Production, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 20-22)
  - The Shakespeare Project, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Shapiro & Smith Dance, 1991-1993 (Box 29, Folder 24-25)
  - Shaun Irons & Lauren Petty, 2004-2009 (Box 29, Folder 26-28)
  - Shen Wei Dance Arts, 2002-2009 (Box 29, Folder 29-33)
  - Sibyl Kempson, 2009-2010 (Box 29, Folder 34-35)
  - Signature Theatre Company, 1995-2004 (Box 29, Folder 36-38)
  - Six-Fifty-One (651) / Kings Majestic Co., 1993-2001 (Box 29, Folder 39-40)
  - Skowhegan School of Painting & Sculpture, 1985-1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Smack Mellon Studios, 2002-2010 (Box 30, Folder 2-8)
  - Snug Harbor Cultural Center, 1992-2010 (Box 30, Folder 9-16)
  - So Percussion, 2009-2010 (Box 30, Folder 17-18)
  - Socrates Sculpture Park, 1996-2009 (Box 30, Folder 19-25)
  - Soho Repertory Theatre, Inc., 2008-2011 (Box 30, Folder 26-28)
  - Soho Repertory Theatre, Inc., 1991-2007 (Box 31, Folder 1-9)
  - Soho Think Tank, 2005-2009 (Box 31, Folder 10-14)
  - Sound Portraits Production, 1997-2000 (Box 31, Folder 15-16)
  - South Street Seaport Museum, 2000-2002 (Box 31, Folder 17-18)
  - Speculum Musicae, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Staten Island Botanical Garden, 1996-1997 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Stephan Koplowitz, 1995-1999 (Box 31, Folder 21-23)
  - Stephen Petronio Company, 1991-1993 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Storefront for Art and Architecture, 1992-2002 (Box 31, Folder 25-32)
  - Streb / Ringside (Elizabeth Streb), 1992-2002 (Box 31, Folder 33-35)
  - Studio Museum in Harlem, 2007-2010 (Box 31, Folder 36-37)
  - Studio Museum in Harlem, 1990-2006 (Box 32, Folder 1-11)
  - Summerstage, 1992-1996 (Box 32, Folder 12-13)
  - Susan Botti / Subo Music, 1994-1997 (Box 32, Folder 14-15)
  - Susan Marshall and Company, 1987-1994 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Swiss Institute of New York, The, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Symphony Space, 1993-2006 (Box 32, Folder 18-24)
  - Tank, The, 2007-2008 (Box 32, Folder 25-26)
  - Target Margin Theater, 1997-2005 (Box 32, Folder 27-31)
  - TEAM, The, 2006-2010 (Box 33, Folder 1-4)
  - Tectonic Theater Project, 2001-2004 (Box 33, Folder 5-6)
  - Tempporary Distortion, 2008-2010 (Box 33, Folder 7-8)
  - Theater Mitu, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Theatre for a New Audience, 1997-2010 (Box 33, Folder 10-13)
  - Theodore Wiprud, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Thirteen P (13P), 2006 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Thirteen / WNET, 1996-2001 (Box 33, Folder 16-19)
  - Thread Waxing Space, 1994-2000 (Box 33, Folder 20-21)
  - Three-Legged Dog, 1997-2002 (Box 33, Folder 22-24)
  - Thundergulch, 1999-2002 (Box 33, Folder 25-30)
  - Tiny Mythic Theatre Co., 1996-1997 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Toby Twining Music, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Todo Con Nada, 1997-1999 (Box 33, Folder 33-34)
  - Triangle Theatre Company, 1989-1994 (Box 33, Folder 35-36)
  - Triple Candie, 2003-2006 (Box 33, Folder 37-39)
  - Trisha Brown Company, 1988-1991 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Under One Roof, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Urban Bush Women, 1989-2006 (Box 34, Folder 2-5)
  - Urban Institute, 2001-2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Via Theater, 1995-1997 (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
  - Vicious Bear Productions, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Vineyard Theatre, 1989-2004 (Box 34, Folder 10-17)
  - Visual Arts Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Voice and Vision, 1999-2000 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Washington Square Arts, 2001 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Washington Square Films, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Waterwell, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Wave Hill, 2000-2010 (Box 34, Folder 23-29)
  - Wax Factory, The, 2007-2009 (Box 34, Folder 30-31)
  - White Box, 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 1-2)
  - White Columns, 2003-2005 (Box 35, Folder 3-5)
  - White Plains Hospital Center, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1987-2001 (Box 35, Folder 7-11)
  - WNYC Radio, 1993-2008 (Box 35, Folder 12-14)
  - Women's Project & Productions, 1990-1997 (Box 35, Folder 15-16)
  - Wooster Group, 1992-2001 (Box 35, Folder 17-19)
  - World Music Institute, 1991-2003 (Box 35, Folder 20-22)
  - W.P.A. Theatre, 1989-1998 (Box 35, Folder 23-24)
  - Writers Voice, The, 1991-1995 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - X-Art, 1997-1999 (Box 35, Folder 26-27)
  - Yasuko Yokoshi, 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 28-29)
  - Yin Mei Dance, 1991-2003 (Box 35, Folder 30-31)
  - Young Concert Artists, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Young Jean Lee's Theater Company, 2007-2010 (Box 35, Folder 33-35)
- Series II: Media
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual material has not been preserved and may not be available to reseachers.
  This series contains CDs, DVDs, VHS tapes, and CD-R data CDs that were sent to the Greenwall Foundation by artists and companies who had applied for and / or recieved grants.
  - Subseries A: Access Copies
    There are currently no access copies for this collection.
  - Subseries B: Originals
    - The Academy of American Poets: Donnelly, Marvin, Shankar, 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0046)
    - Adam Silverman - "Chamber Music", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0047)
    - American Composers Orchestra - Greenwall application, Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0048)
    - American Composers Orchestra - Greenwall proposal, 2009; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0049)
    - American Contemporary Music Ensemble, Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0050)
    - Americas Society - "Music of the Americas", 2008; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0051)
    - The Barbad Chamber Orchestra, 2006; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0052)
    - Bright Sheng - "H'un (Lacerations) and Other Works", 1991; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0001)
    - Bruce Odland - "Leaving Eden", 1991; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0053)
    - Bruce Odland - "Time Tunnels", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0054)
    - Califia, 1997; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0002)
    - "The Composer's Voice: New Music from Bowling Green", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0003)
    - The Corigliano Quartet, Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0055)
    - Daniel Schnyder - "Revelation of St. John", 2004; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0056)
    - Darkling: a music-theatre piece, Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0057)
    - Festival Chamber Music presents: Athena Adamopoulos, 2011; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0058)
      General note
      Wrapped in plastic.
    - Festival Chamber Music: Live in Concert, 2004; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0059)
    - GIA Conference: Taos Journey - Southwest Sound Sampler, 2007; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0060)
    - The Golden Gate: An Opera in Two Acts, 2008; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0061)
    - Hip Hop Orchestra - "Dakah", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0062)
    - ICElab 2012 New York Artists Work Samples, Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0014)
    - Issue Project Room, Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0063)
    - Janacek Philharmonic Orchestra, 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0064)
    - Jazz at Lincoln Center - "A Decade with Duke", 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0065)
    - Jazz at Lincoln Center - "Essentially Ellington", 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0066)
    - Jefferson Friedman - "Chiara String Quartet", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0067)
    - Jefferson Friedman - "Eight Songs, based on music by Crom-Teck", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0068)
    - "The Jewish Giant: A Sound Portrait", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0004)
      Wrapped in plastic
    - John Adams - "Son of Chamber Symphony String Quartet", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0069)
    - Kevin James - "Portraits (Sample)", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0015)
    - Kitzke, Jerome - "The Character of American Sunlight", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0005)
    - Kono Michi - "The Livingroom Disappearance E.P.", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0070)
    - Lependorf / Goodrich - "The Art of Eating", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0071)
    - Lependorf / Sherman - "Oh, Bill, Oh, Susan", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0072)
    - Makoto Nakura - "Triple Jump", 2004; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0073)
    - Ned Rorem - "Evidence of Things not Seen", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0006)
      Two discs, labeled "a" and "b"
    - "New York: Music from the Soundtrack", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0007)
    - The Orchestra of the S.E.M. Ensemble - "Composer's Workshop Concert", 1999; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0013)
    - Patricia Burgess - "Reflections of the Watermoon", 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0074)
    - Patricia Burgess - "Reflections of the Watermoon", 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0075)
    - Patrick Zimmerli - "Phoenix", 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0076)
    - Perry Townsend - "No Suggestion of Silence", 2001; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0077)
    - Randall Woolf - "Rock Steady" (Emergency Music series), 1998; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0008)
    - The Renaldo The Ensemble - "Why Are You?", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0078)
    - Sappho Fragments: For alto voice and piano, 2005; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0079)
    - Sebastian Currier, 1997; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0009)
    - Slow Six - "Private Times in Public Places", 2004; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0080)
    - Susan Botti - ""Listen, It's Snowing" (Emergency Music series), 1998; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0010)
    - Susan Botti - "Telaio: Desdemona", 1995; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0011)
    - Svet Stoyanov - "Percussive Counterpoint", Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0081)
    - Talea Ensemble, Undated; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0082)
    - "Under the Silver Moon", 2000; Format: CD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0012)
      No disc
    - The World/Inferno Friendship Society - "Just the Best Party", 2002; Format: CD (Box 36, Disk ID: 336.0083)
    - "Amato: A Love Affair with Opera", Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0016)
    - "Beyond Woods: The Marriage of Art and Literature in Bookmaking", 1994; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0017)
    - The Builders Association - "Master Builder", 1994; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0018)
    - The Builders Association - "The White Album", 1995; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0019)
    - The Builders Association - "Xtravaganza", 2000; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0020)
    - Compania Pendiante (Barcelona), Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0021)
    - Dendy Dance - "Dream Analysis", 1998; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0022)
    - Distillations - Alain le Razer, 1994; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0023)
    - Donna Uchinzono Company, 1999; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0024)
    - Eliza Miller Dance Company, 2001; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0025)
    - The Flying Machine Theater - "Archipelago", 2000; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0026)
    - The Flying Machine Theater - "Signals of Distress", 2001; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0027)
    - Golan Levin - "Audiovisual Environment Suite", 2000; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0028)
    - Golan Levin - "Dialtones: A Telesymphony", 2001; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0029)
    - La Otra Orilla Pregones Theater, Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0030)
    - Limon Dance Company, Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0031)
    - Limon Dance Company in Adam Hougland's "Phantasy Quintet", 2002; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0032)
    - Lorn MacDougal and Alain le Razer in "Dance & Film", 1991; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0033)
    - Mark Morris Dance Group - "Dido and Aeneas", Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0034)
    - "Moment of Impact" - Julia Loktev, excerpt from work in progress, 1997; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0035)
    - Nicholas Leichter Dance - "Free the Angels, Undertow", 2001; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0036)
    - O'Day Dances, 1998; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0037)
    - Pregones Theater - "Translated Woman", 1998; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0038)
    - "Scrawl", 1999; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0039)
    - WNET - "Amato: A Love Affair with Opera", 2001; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0040)
    - WNET - "Reel New York #301", Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0041)
    - WNET - "Reel New York #302", Undated; Format: VHS (Box 36, Cassette ID: 336.0042)
    - 2007: The Videos, Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0043)
    - Artichoke Dance company - dances by Lynn Neuman, 2004; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0084)
    - Bent Festival, 2008; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0085)
    - Bronx Museum - Connect, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0086)
    - Bronx Museum - Vito Acconci (copy 1), 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0087)
    - Bronx Museum - Vito Acconci (copy 2), 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0088)
    - BYOD - Randall Woolf and Valeria Vasilevski, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0089)
    - Clare Byrne Dance presents - "Sweet Chariots", 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0090)
    - Dead Man Dancing EXCESS, 2004; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0091)
    - Exit Art - Love / War / Sex, 2007; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0092)
    - Exit Art - Praying Project, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0093)
    - Exit Art and Trickster Theater - Tropical Area, 2007; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0094)
    - Fathom, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0095)
    - Figment festival, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0096)
    - Four Short Plays, Four Big Ideas, 2007; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0097)
    - Franklin Furnace - The Theater of a Two-Headed Calf - work samples, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0098)
    - Harvostworks Surround Sound, Silk Mill, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0099)
    - Ibrahim Quraishi - Ring, 2002; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0100)
    - Ibrahim Quraishi - Rivage a l'abandon, Munich, 2002; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0101)
    - Ibrahim Quraishi - Rivage a l'abandon, Nantes France, 2000; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0102)
    - ICE at Oberlin, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0103)
    - Jerome Robbins' NY Export: Opus Jazz, The Film, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0104)
    - Kate Weare - "Drop Down", 2006; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0044)
    - Kate Weare - "Wet Road", 2006; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0045)
    - Limon, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0105)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      DVD is broken
    - Medea in Aia, 2006; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0106)
    - Media that Matters Film Festival, 2008; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0107)
    - Miguel Gutierrez and the Powerful People - "Retrospective Exhibitionist and Difficult Bodies", 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0108)
    - Palissimo, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0109)
    - Paul's Case - highlights, 2009; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0110)
    - So Percussion - work samples, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0111)
    - St. Ann's Warehouse, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0112)
    - Tseng Yu-Chin video collection, 2003-2008; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0113)
      Three discs, labeled a, b, and c
    - TULP the Body Public, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0114)
    - White Wave - Wave Rising Series, 2007; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0115)
    - Who Needs Orchestras?, 2005; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0116)
    - The Wind Up Bird Chronicle: A Multimedia Play in Development, Undated; Format: DVD (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.0117)
      No disc.
    - Creative Drive - beta test version, Undated; Format: CD-R (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0009)
    - Exit Art - history, Undated; Format: CD-R (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0010)
    - George Booryjy - images, 2007; Format: CD-R (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0011)
    - Gift Works - Fundraising software, 2003; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0001)
    - Harmonic Progression - screening sample (MAC version), 2004; Format: CD-R (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0012)
    - Harmonic Progression - screening sample (PC format), 2004; Format: CD-R (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0013)
    - Julia Heyward, Multi-Media Artist - "Miracles in Reverse", Undated; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0002)
    - Lower Manhattan Cultural Council Request to the Greenwall Foundation, Undated; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0003)
    - Matthew - slides, 2007; Format: CD-R (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0014)
    - The Past Present: History for Public Radio, Undated; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0004)
    - Steve Miller, Undated; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0005)
    - Steve Miller - "Dreaming Brain", 1999; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0006)
    - Steve Miller - "Dreaming Brain" beta version, 1999; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0007)
    - "Two Studies for 'The Sparks, The Ringing' composed by Andrew Warshaw", Undated; Format: CD-Rom (Box 37, Disk ID: 336.3.0008)
  - Subseries C: Papers removed from media
    - DVD labels and loose material - various artists, Undated (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0000b)
    - Susan [Botti] - card, 1998 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0010b)
    - Dendy Dance - "Dream Analysis" program and letter, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0022b)
    - O'Day Dances - VHS label, 1998 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0037b)
    - Pregones Theater - letter, 2000 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0038b)
    - WNET - "Reel New York" season III - letter, 1998 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0041b)
    - The Corigliano Quartet - letter, 2006 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0055b)
    - Medea in Aia - letter, 2006 (Box 35, Folder ID: 336.0106b)
- Series III: Objects
  - Ballet de Monterrey - Calendario (in a CD case), 2009 (Box 38)
  - Creative Time / DNAid - "How Will the Future Be Different" paper cups, Undated (Box 38)
  - Justine Cooper - "Havitol: When More is Not Enough" package - DVD, "pills", mousepad, t-shirt., 2007 (Box 38)